[{"answer": "Well, I don't -- that's what I want to know, because everybody's talking about it, that this is a show.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Why would it be a show?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "ILLER: You know, Piers, it actually works either way.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "With all your expert knowledge of bomb making and bombs, is it likely that they could have pulled off this Boston marathon double bombing in the extremely efficient successful way that they did without having physically trained with similar devices, at least Tamerlan, back in somewhere like Dagestan?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, they're not really warnings.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Are those not enough to trigger real alarm bells?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "John, stay with me.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "I'd be very curious to say, if he was a threat to the Russians, what did they do with him while he was on their turf?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Piers, I don't think anyone that I know of was foolish enough to give that sort of assurance.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Have we seen exactly the same thing happen again here?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a little early to say that al Qaeda is not part of the problem as well.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Is that the new phase of the war on terror?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, it would appear that we have but it seems to me the red line should have been something much, much earlier.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Have we crossed that red line by that criteria, and if so, what should the president be doing about it?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, I think you framed the argument there.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Or was there a duty of care, if you like, to an American citizen, as Dzhokhar is, to give him his Miranda rights at that time?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well, he sounds so far like a charismatic recruiter.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I think, you know, we have to trace it back, Piers, to say how did this whole thing start.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "How much of it is deserved?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Yeah, she was very serious.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "I mean, her injuries were pretty serious?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Well, it's nuts.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "What is your feeling towards them from what they've done to your fiance?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "You know, Aaron has made an amazing recovery, actually.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "First of all, how is Aaron, your little boy?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "His reaction, it was one of -- it's been a lot of things.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "What has been his reaction to the fact that somebody just turned up to bomb people?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Oh, it was wonderful.", "docId": "130425pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "How did that go?", "qSentId": 435}]